Alexa Artis Hi there.

SUMMARY

Passionate photographer, web developer and digital creator highly skilled in the Adobe Creative Suite, HTML, and CSS. I have over four years of experience managing and updating websites in WordPress, and 10 years of experience with landscape, portrait, and documentary photography in both digital and analog formats and am currently seeking my Part 107 cert for drone photography. I strive to creative beautiful, accessible art through code and photography that is elegant and functional as well. I am willing to relocate anywhere globally.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER 2019 - PRESENT

Develops and designs website and branding materials from scratch using various scripting languages and applications. Prepares drafts of designs and wireframes for client approval. Performs routine site audits and ongoing maintenance. Oversees the analyzing, writing, building, and deployment of websites from start-to-finish. Utilizes iOS terminal, VS Code, Git, Glitch and other applications and services to deploy and maintain websites.

OPERATIONS SPECIALIST, TRITON LIGHT MEDICAL LLC 2019 - PRESENT Assists the company principal in planning, organizing and coordinating functions relating to the operation of the business. Provides recommendations and suggestions for improvements in aspects relating to sales strategies, social media strategies, and website management.

DIGITAL MEDIA CONSULTANT, NCSU LIBRARIES 2019 - 2022

Taught library patrons media creation and editing through auditory and visual mediums. Led one-on-one technology consultations, assisting with individual or group projects that dealt with photography and video editing. Developed and presented State of Exposure workshops for basic and intermediate digital photography students.

OFFICE ASSISTANT, NCSU COLLEGE OF NATURAL RESOURCES 2018 - 2019 Performed administrative support tasks, including updating and sorting files, and conducting research. Designed and produced calendars with a focus on DEI. Managed and distributed inventory to colleagues and classmates facing food insecurity. Authored an <u>opinion piece</u> on how food and housing insecurity impact NC State students.

EDUCATION

NC STATE UNIVERSITY - B.A. INTERNATIONAL STUDIES WITH A MINOR IN PHILOSOPHY (ANTICIPATED 2023)

SKILLS

Languages: HTML5, CSS, PHP, JavaScript // CMS: WordPress, Wix // Applications: GitHub, InVision, DaVinci Resolve, Adobe Creative Suite, Glitch, VS Code // Languages: English, Portuguese (intrmd)